“创始吸血鬼”前情提要
KLAUS: Previously on The Originals...
这座城市曾经是我的家
我不在的日子里
This town was my home once
and in my absence,
马赛尔得到了我想要的一切
Marcel has got
everything I ever wanted.
我要夺回来
I want it back.
我在此宣誓效忠于你
I hereby pledge
my allegiance to you.
- 莎莉丝特
- 莎莉丝特？
-Celeste.
-Celeste?
不管她是谁，她确实非常性感
Whoever she was,
she was smoking hot.
我相信当你深爱着一个人
I believe that
when you love someone,
你会变得格外脆弱
you're uniquely vulnerable.
是我害死了她
She died because of me.
黛维娜，她是个强大的武器
Davina. She's a powerful weapon.
我知道我该被杀死
I knew that I was supposed
to be killed
以完成收获祭
so the harvest could be completed.
她死了
你听到了吗？
MARCEL: She is dead!
Do you hear me?
四个人本该复活的，但一个都没有
Four were supposed to rise,
and none did.
那些法力去哪了？
Where did all that power go?
有人召唤我们
TUNDE: Someone called us forth.
是谁？
- 是我
-Who?
-SABlNE: I did.
如果你们能叫我的真名，我会很感激的
叫我莎莉丝特
I'd appreciate if you call me
by my real name, Celeste.
我记得这处墓地
一点都没变
I remember this cemetery.
Hasn't changed a bit.
一个世纪来我无数次来到这里
I've been coming here
over a century
每次都是不同的面目
wearing one face or another.
克莱拉桑莫林，你能快点吗？
再不走就什么都看不到了
Clara Summerlin, will you come on?
We're gonna miss everything.
跟你说了吧
法语区的所有女巫都来了
Told you.
Every witch in the Quarter is here.
她们都是来见伟大的图德巫父
Come to see the great Papa Tunde.
法语区的女巫们
谢谢你们的热情欢迎
Witches of the French Quarter,
thank you for your welcome.
很高兴能与有信仰的人共聚一堂
It is good to be among
people of the faith.
和你们一样，我修习的也是祖传魔法
I, too, practice ancestral magic,
向我们的先人致敬
honoring those
who walked the path before us.
从他们的身上汲取力量
From them, we draw strength.
巨大的黑暗即将降临
你们会需要足够的力量与之对抗
And you will need strength,
for a great darkness is coming.
你们祖先留下的城市
The city your forefathers left you
如今正被海盗、野兽
和吸血鬼肆意蹂躏
is now overrun by pirates,
beasts and vampires.
我还修习了另外一种魔法
献祭魔法
TUNDE: I practice other
magic as well... Sacrificial magic...
透过从祭品的生命中汲取力量
Channeling power from
the lives of my offerings,
我利用这些力量来征服我的敌人
I use this strength
to vanquish my enemies.
我也会让你们的敌人为贪婪付出代价
And I will punish
your enemies for their greed.
作为回报，你们要接纳我的家人
In return, you will accept
my family into your coven.
同时，听命于我
And me as your leader.
先生们，请不必狗谨
Gentlemen, make yourselves at home.
欧康诺市长看来有事耽搁了
Mayor O'Connell appears
to be running late
但今天要讨论的很多
所以我们先开始吧
but there's much to discuss,
so I shall begin.
等等我，老哥
KLAUS: One moment please, brother.
你知道我最喜欢参加这种
非法的小集会了
You know how much I enjoy
these illicit, little gatherings.
别担心
ELlJAH: Do not be troubled.
尽管我弟弟声名狼藉
但我向你们保证
Despite my brother's reputation,
I can assure you,
今天请你们来的目的是和谈
we've invited you here
to broker in peace.
我发誓
You have my word.
算你们运气好
我哥哥向来信守他的誓言
And, lucky for you,
my brother always keeps his word.
你们俩是葛雷拉犯罪家族的吧
You two are from
the Guerrera crime family,
一群粗野的盗贼和杀手
a brutish pack of thieves
and killers,
但比起你们在月圆夜的变身
and that's nothing compared
to what you become
- 简直就是小巫见大巫
- 好了，别说了
-on a full moon, is it?
-Yes, yes, yes.
当然了，狼人咬伤对真祖来说并不致命
Of course, a bite from your kind
is not lethal to an Original.
所以我们之间如果起了冲突
你们绝对没有好下场
Conflict between us
would not end well for you at all.
这是我们的提议
Let's state our proposal here.
我们兄弟俩掌握着这个城市的港口
My brother and l
control the ports of the city.
但随着禁酒令即将成为法律在这里实施
But with prohibition
soon to be the law of the land,
联邦对这里的管理会加强
there'll be a certain uptick
这是我们想要避免的
in the kind of federal presence
we prefer to avoid.
因此，我有个提议
Therefore, I'd like to suggest
a system whereby
在我们的监管下
under our supervision, of course.
葛雷拉家族可以
The Guerrera family can traffic alcohol
在纽奥良做贩酒的生意
into the city of
New Orleans for a profit.
一切都还是我们说了算
但我们的规矩仍然不会公开
We would still be in charge
but our rule would remain a secret.
听起来真不错
This all sounds very good.
但请告诉我
这对女巫们有什么好处？
Tell me,
how will it benefit the witches?
抱歉，这是私人集会
I am sorry.
This is a private meeting.
我知道，城市首领间的集会
Yes, for kings of the city.
但我也是首领
我也有我的规矩
But l, too, am a king,
and I have rules.
我很佩服你
I'm impressed.
你还真是野心勃勃，要不就是疯了
You're either quite ambitious
or quite mad.
怎么称呼呢，老兄？
What's your name, mate?
我是阿冯斯贝拉图德戴加洛
信徒们称我为图德巫父
I am Alphonz Bellatunde Delgallo,
Papa Tunde to my followers.
我是来要求你们向女巫们进贡
And I come to ask that the witches
be granted fair tribute
用以换取在这座城市生存的权利
for allowing your existence
in our city.
你的意思是，如今
你代表法语区的女巫吗？
Are you suggesting that you speak
for the French Quarter witches?
没错
I do now.
希望以后我们的谈判能顺利进行
And I expect our future
negotiations to go very smoothly.
为了确保这一点
我带来了一份礼物
As a guarantee, I brought a gift.
期待我们下一次的会面
I await our next gathering.
我想我们需要找个新市长了
Well, I suppose
we'll need a new mayor.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：巫师的复仇
马赛尔
主演：约瑟夫摩根
Hey, Marcel,
或许你知道是怎么回事
maybe you know what's going on.
克劳斯召集大伙过来
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
Klaus ordered us to meet here
他自己却不出现
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
and now he's a no-show.
你想要我怎么样？
主演：克莱儿荷特
What do you want from me?
如今是新的政权了
主演：克莱儿荷特
It's a new regime.
开始习惯吧
Get used to it.
亲爱的弟兄们，请听我说
主演：菲比托金
KLAUS: Dearest brethren,
your attention, please.
我相信你们一定会很惊讶
见到提艾里范舒
No doubt, you're all surprised
to see Thierry Vanchure,
一个因为杀害自己同胞
who's supposed to be
rotting in the garden
而本该在花园里腐烂的人
for the crime of killing
one of our own.
如今我决定亲自赦免他
And I personally decided
to issue him with a pardon.
希望你们都能热烈欢迎
I hope you'll all
提艾里回归
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
welcome home Thierry.
欢迎回来，兄弟
Welcome home, mate.
你看起来心情不错
You're in a good mood.
你应该多去几趟迷瀑镇
You should visit
Mystic Falls more often.
尽管我也想那么做
Well, as much as I might like to,
但我在这有更紧急的事要处理
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
I have pressing responsibilities here.
你们都知道
Now, as you all know,
女巫黛维娜已经离我们而去了
主演：莉雅派普斯
the witch Davina
is no longer with us.
没有了她，我们就没法继续监视
Without Davina,
we can no longer monitor
那些女巫邻居的一举一动
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
the activity
of our witch neighbors.
然而，由于收获祭的失败
However, since their Harvest failed,
她们很快就会永远失去法力
their magic
will soon be gone forever.
但在那之前，我们还是给她们点警告
Until then,
I say we keep them on their toes.
迪亚哥，我想请你带着兄弟们
去女巫区骚扰一下
Diego, I wonder if you might lead
a rousting in the cauldron.
兄弟们上吧
DlEGO: Let's do it.
马赛尔，我希望你能跟迪亚哥一起去
Marcel, I'd hoped
you would join Diego.
不了
Nah.
我今天请个假
I'm gonna take a personal day.
你尽管可以怀疑他
ELlJAH: Now, you may doubt him.
今天我见到尼克劳斯
对敌人展现出了仁慈
Today, I saw Niklaus demonstrate
mercy towards an enemy.
- 这难道不是进步吗？
- 得了吧，以利亚
-Tell me that's not progress.
-Please, Elijah.
你觉得是谁说服克劳斯
放提艾里出来的？
Who do you think convinced
Klaus to let Thierry out?
你为什么要这么做？
Why would you do such a thing?
因为尽管克劳斯放了他
Because, despite Klaus' reprieve,
提艾里仍鄙视他
制片：兰斯安德森
Thierry despises him.
我就喜欢提艾里这一点
I like that about Thierry.
我还喜欢他曾与女巫约会过
I also like that he used
to date a witch,
这样他对法语区的女巫也很熟悉
so he knows about
French Quarter covens.
或许他能帮我找到
Maybe he can lead me
偷取了收获祭法力的人
to whoever stole off
with the Harvest magic.
蕾贝卡
我们都对仪式的结果感到难过
Rebekah, we are all devastated
by the outcome of this ritual.
这就是问题所在，没有结果
That's just it.
There was no outcome.
我们都清楚那么强大的法力
不可能凭空消失
We both know that power like that
doesn't just vanish.
我认为有人偷了它
I say someone stole it.
我想知道是谁
制片：邦妮怀斯
I'd like to know who
然后与他们结成盟友
制片：邦妮怀斯
and then I'd like
to make an ally out of them.
到底是为了什么呢？
To what end, exactly?
我已经受够我们那暴虐的兄弟
I'm tired of being threatened
and controlled
终日的威胁与控制了
by our tyrant brother.
如果你要阻止一个恶徒
If you want to stop a bully,
你就必须要有足够的力量对抗他
you need the power
to stand up to them.
尼克劳斯这么干我不意外
I expect such behavior from Niklaus.
但你有这种想法
让我非常失望，蕾贝卡
It's so very disappointing
when it comes from you, Rebekah.
难道你没发现，他在用自己的方式
努力尝试改变吗？
Do you not see that in his way,
he's making an effort here?
他邀请我们回到那属于我们的家
编剧：麦可鲁梭，麦克纳度奇
He's invited us back
into our family home.
他渴望我们家族再次团聚
He yearns for our family
to be reunited.
对，他现在是心情不错
但这能持续多久呢？
Yes. He's in a brilliant mood now
but for how long?
这是他的诡计，以利亚
It's his trick, Elijah.
他先安抚你，给你一种…
He lulls you into a false sense
友情和亲情的错觉
导演：罗伯哈迪
of camaraderie and kinship
然后在一瞬间背叛你
and then he turns
on you like a snake.
我每次都上当
I fall for it every time
下场就是胸口上插着匕首
and wind up with a dagger
in my chest for my trouble.
我不要再这样了
No more.
我相信他正达到
一种近乎平和的境界
I believe that he is approaching
some semblance of peace here.
成为首领也许对他来说是件好事
Leadership may, in fact,
be a good thing for him.
现在，我请求你
如果你不能支持他
Now, sister, please, I ask you,
if you cannot support him,
至少别做任何会激怒他的事
then at least do nothing
to provoke him.
结果就是这样吗？
KLAUS: Is this what's it's come to?
我一个人肩负整个王国的重任
I bear the full weight
of our kingdom
而你在旁像个小孩一样闹脾气
while you pout like a child.
是你自己想当国王
You wanted to be King.
再说，你看来已经掌控住局面了
Besides, you look like
you got it covered.
如果手下看到你这副不负责任的样子
If the men see you
shirk your duties,
他们很可能也会这么做
they're likely to do the same.
我说过了，我没心情参加什么
吸血鬼的胡闹
I told you, I am not in
the mood for vampire hijinx.
是啊，你宁愿坐在这借酒浇愁
No. You'd rather sit
wallowing in sorrow
哀悼你的小朋友
for your lost little friend.
你最好别逼我
Don't push me right now!
黛维娜不在了我也很难过好吗？
我很遗憾
I am sorry Davina is gone, okay?
I'm sorry,
但这么一直消沉下去也于事无补
but this mournful attitude
is unworthy of you
我都快受不了你这臭脸了
and it's boring to me.
嘿，两位
我们遇到麻烦了
Hey guys, we got a problem.
我们按你说的，去找女巫的麻烦
We came to mess with the witches,
just like you said,
接着这两个弟兄失踪了
找到他们时就是这样了
and these two, they went missing,
found them like this.
身上甚至没插木桩，就这么死了
Not even staked, just dead.
你去哪？
Where are you going?
我们必须找出是谁干的
Someone has to account for this.
你想要复仇，自己去吧
You want revenge, get it yourself.
那个符号跟一种可怕的巫术有关
That mark is tied to some bad mojo.
你们如果有点脑子
就该赶紧回去
Any of y'all got any brains,
you'll head back to the compound
别插手此事
and stay the hell out of this.
我们要找出是谁干的
We're gonna find whoever did this,
然后让他们好好尝尝苦头
and I will show them
what suffering is.
我以前曾在这里帮马赛尔办事
THlERRY: Used to run
things down here for Marcel.
我想在报告给克劳斯之前先让你看看
Thought you'd like to see
what I found before Klaus did.
才刚从花园被放出来
Not a day out of the garden
你就立刻证明自己的用处了
and you're already
proving yourself useful.
这是我们达成的协定
We made a deal,
只要能坏你哥哥的好事
我会全力以赴
and if it screws things
for your brother, I'm all for it.
但老实说，这玩意让我毛骨悚然
Though, to be honest,
this stuff makes my skin crawl.
我从没见过这样的阵法
I've never seen anything like this.
我见过，很久很久以前
I have, a long time ago.
有人在模仿一个非常危险的巫师
Somebody is copycatting
a very dangerous witch.
他们以献祭获取法力
They draw their power
from sacrifice.
我只是不明白
I just don't understand
为什么会有人把阵法留下让我们找到
why someone would
leave it here for us to find.
除非他们是故意想被找到
Unless they wanted it to be found.
米卡森小姐
TUNDE: Mademoiselle Mikaelson.
- 这不可能
- 当然可能，亲爱的，这可是魔法
-That's not possible.
-Sure, it is, cherie. It's magic.
我一定要让他血债血偿
KLAUS: Someone will die for this.
出乎意料地，我并无异议
ELlJAH: Remarkably, I don't disagree.
但我想知道
他们从哪学的黑魔法
However, I would like to know
where they learned such dark magic.
我曾希望再也不要见到这符号
I had hoped never to see
that symbol again.
我记得这符号属于一个曾妄想
I recall it is the signature
of a fool
对付我们的傻子
who once stood against us.
显然有自命不凡的巫师试图故技重施
Clearly, some upstart witch
is salvaging old tricks.
我会像对之前那个一样处置他
I'll do for him as I did the other.
迪亚哥
Diego.
夜慕降临后
When night falls,
我要你召集法语区所有的吸血鬼
I want you to gather
every vampire in the Quarter.
把罪魁祸首的人头给我带来
然后把它插在一根棍子上
Get me the head of whoever did this,
and put it on a stick.
这可能有点问题
Yeah.
That's gonna be a problem.
大家都吓坏了，老大
Everyone is freaked out, man.
好久都没有吸血鬼死在巫师手上了
We haven't had witches
killing vampires in a long time.
马赛尔把我们保护得很好
Marcel made sure of that.
马赛尔像个被吓坏的小孩一样跑了
Marcel has run off like a scared child.
你们只能跟着我了
You lot are left with me.
现在，你们中哪一位
愿意为捍卫家园而战？
Now, who of you will fight
to defend our home?
没人愿意与我并肩作战
Not a single one of you
will stand with me,
你们就如此惧怕这个新的威胁吗？
so afraid are you of this new threat?
你们真该放聪明点
You should know better.
这事我亲自去处理
I'll handle this myself.
苏菲，赛厅里又乱成一团了
Sophie, the restaurant
is an epic disaster, again.
你今天能过来一趟吗…
Do you think maybe
you could come in today and--
用户的语音信箱已满，再见
AUTOMATED VOlCE:
User's mailbox is full. Goodbye.
看来我昨晚就该过来
Looks like I should've
been here last night.
你少轻举妄动，我体内有马鞭草
Before you try anything,
I'm on vervain.
知道，克劳斯说过你摆脱了他的魅惑
Yeah. Klaus mentioned
you broke free of his compulsion.
真不错
Good for you.
- 苏菲在吗？
- 不在，你找她干嘛？
-Sophie around?
-No. Why?
有个关于巫师的问题
我想她应该知道答案
Got a witch problem.
Thought she might have answers.
介意我在这等吗？
Mind if I wait?
大白天就开始喝酒
让我猜猜，克劳斯的问题
It's a little early for day drinking.
Let me guess, Klaus problems.
我还以为你们现在正高兴着呢
I thought you'd be
on top of the world
黛维娜都被你们给抓回去了
now that you have Davina back.
黛维娜死了
Davina is gone.
是克劳斯干的吗？
我警告过他，如果他敢伤害她…
Was it Klaus?
I told him, if he hurt her--
不是他干的
It wasn't like that.
她体内的法力太强
The power that she had was too much.
我们试图用一个疯狂的仪式
助她稳定法力
We tried to fix her
with this crazy-ass ritual,
结果出了问题
现在她…
and something went wrong.
Now she's--
我也不知道，也许正游荡在地狱边缘
或是等着她的先祖显灵什么的
I don't know. Floating in limbo
or waiting on her ancestors.
马赛尔
Marcel.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
是啊，我也很遗憾
Yeah. Me, too.
- 你在这呢
- 我就在这呢
-There you are.
-Here I am.
这些是黛维娜的画
Davina's drawings.
是的，很恐怖，我知道
Yeah. Morbid, I know.
但我在想，我们一直没搞清楚
I was just thinking,
we never figured out
她为什么要画莎莉丝特
why she drew those
pictures of Celeste.
反正我也只是在消磨时间
既然我被吸血鬼关了禁闭
Anyway, I'm just killing time now
that I'm on vampire lockdown.
不管是谁干的，我们会想办法处理
事情很快就能解决
Whoever did this, we will deal
with them. It won't be long.
我不担心这个
I'm not worried.
只是觉得可笑的是
Just think it's kind of funny
得有重大的超自然威胁
that it took some big, supernatural threat
你才肯和我共处一室
for you to even come
into the same room as me.
若让你感到被怠慢了，我很抱歉
I do apologize
if you feel neglected.
我最近一直很忙
I have been occupied.
我的弟弟妹妹正在闹别扭
尼克劳斯又一直很焦躁
My siblings are in some quarrel.
Niklaus remains agitated.
你也记得，我们之间再短暂的交流
You'll recall that even
our slightest interactions
都会…激怒他
seem to infuriate him.
所以说克劳斯是个混蛋
而你想当个好哥哥
So Klaus is a dick,
and you want to be a good big brother.
所以我们不能在一起
So, we can't hang out.
概括起来是这样吗？
That sum it up?
我明白，以利亚
只是觉得这情形有够糟糕的
I get it, Elijah.
It just seems like a really crappy deal.
领袖的召唤吗？
El presidente?
他喜欢掌控手下的行踪
He likes to keep track of his people.
你为什么要效忠于他？
Why are you loyal to him, exactly?
你不是说受不了他吗
You know, for someone who says
she can't stand the guy,
干嘛一直追问关于他的事？
you sure ask a lot of questions
about him.
- 这只是纯学术性的好奇
- 我知道你想干嘛
-My interest is purely academic.
-I know what you're doing.
你气他利用你，想要报复他
You're mad he used you
and you wanna get back at him.
也许你在套我的话
希望我说出他的弱点
Maybe you're hoping I'll let slip
some chink in his armor.
给你句忠告，别干傻事
Friendly advice, don't do that.
不会有好下场
It won't end well.
我来跟你讲个试图
Let me tell you a story
about someone
对付克劳斯的人的故事吧
who went up against Klaus.
那时我刚从一战的战场回来
MARCEL: This was right after
I returned from World War I.
我一直想离开纽奥良
I'd been trying to get away
from New Orleans for a while.
（欢迎回家）
但却一直被吸引回来
But something kept drawing me back.
你不对我说欢迎回来吗？
Aren't you gonna welcome me home?
我不想让你觉得我很高兴见到你
I wouldn't want you to think
that I was happy to see you.
你还要恨我多久？
How long you gonna hate me?
你让我在棺材里躺了52年
少说也得恨上个100年吧
You left me in a box for 52 years.
Twice that seems like a good start.
走吧，小伙子们
Come on, boys.
他在这呢
战争英雄凯旋归来啦
There he is.
Our war hero triumphantly returned.
你回来了我很高兴，马赛勒斯
Oh, good to have you back, Marcellus.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
回头的浪子总算把酒量
The prodigal son
has finally learned
给练出来了
to hold his liquor.
- 都是军队的功劳
- 你能回来我们都很高兴
-The army'll do that to you.
-Well, it's good to have you back.
你不在尼克劳斯都快疯了
Niklaus was beside himself
in your absence.
既然你回来了
Now that you are here,
也许你能帮我们评评理
perhaps you could help
settle an argument.
国外的战争打完了
这里的战役又开始了
You see, you've traded a war abroad
for one here in the Quarter.
有个流氓巫师
想在我们建立的城市中分一杯羹
Some rogue witch
wants a piece of the city we built,
让我无法理解的是，以利亚居然
and Elijah, for reasons
beyond my comprehension,
坚持要以协商来解决分歧
insists that negotiation
is our best recourse.
好吧，既然说到无法理解的事
Yes. On the topic
of your failed comprehension,
你忘了，身为一名军人
马赛尔已见识过
you forget, as a soldier,
Marcel has seen
世界现在变得有多小
not only how small the world
has become
以及消息传播速度之快
and how fast news can travel,
但最重要的是，战争的恐怖之处
but also,
the very horrors of war itself.
理所当然，马赛尔会认同我的做法
Surely, Marcel would agree with me.
要想捍卫我们的家园，最好的办法
The best way for us
to defend our home
就是谨慎行事
is by exercising discretion.
你想杀的巫师是谁？
So, who's the witch
you wanted to kill?
他叫图德巫父
His name is Papa Tunde.
我觉得他只是个江湖骗子
I think he's a charlatan.
马赛尔很快就能自己判断他的为人了
Well, Marcel shall be able
to decide that for himself.
- 你还邀请了他
- 当然
-You invited him here.
-Of course.
我们又不是野蛮人
，对吧？
We're not savages, aren't we?
谢谢你应邀前来
欢迎
Thank you for accepting
our invitation, and welcome.
希望你能让我尽地主之谊
I hope you'll allow me
to play the role of host.
如果你们需要任何东西
If there's anything you need...
敬请随意享用
Anything at all....
那就先娱乐再谈正事了
Pleasure before business, then.
起初我并不明白
MARCEL ; I didn't get it at first.
想要挑起战争的是克劳斯
Klaus was the one
who wanted to go to war.
那他为什么要把敌人邀请到家中来？
So, why was he inviting his enemy
into his home?
为什么要慷慨招待自己欲杀之人？
Why be so generous to someone
who he's gonna have to kill?
但要知道，这就是关键所在
But, you see, that's the thing.
这一切都是克劳斯密谋的计划
It was all part of Klaus' plan.
他是在试探敌方的底细
He was sussing the guy out,
模清他的弱点与实力
Iearning his weaknesses,
his strengths,
让他放下防备
getting him to let his guard down.
这就是克劳斯的作风
最后再一举灭敌
That's how Klaus does it.
Then he goes in for the kill.
因为他是个人面兽心的反社会变态
Because he's a two-faced sociopath.
克劳斯的所作所为没什么好羡慕的
There's nothing enviable
about what Klaus does.
他是个怪物
He's a monster.
我们都是怪物，卡蜜
We're all monsters, Cami.
如果你像克劳斯那样强大
If you're powerful like Klaus is,
你也会不屑于隐藏的
you just don't have
to bother hiding it.
黛维娜也很强大
Davina was powerful.
但她不是怪物
She wasn't a monster.
仪式完成了
PAPA TUNDE: It is done.
真祖妹妹的力量传给了我
The power of the Original sister
flows through me.
这力量足以让克劳斯生不如死吗？
And will that be enough
to make Klaus suffer?
克劳斯米卡森当初对我的伤害
我会以牙还牙的
I will hurt Klaus Mikaelson
as he hurt me.
等我完成
他会祈求自己能早点解脱
When I am done,
he will wish that he could die.
- 你今天打算营业吗？
- 冒着让你吃掉客人的风险吗？
-You gonna open this place today?
-And risk you eating the clientele?
我还以为你又开始喜欢我了呢
Oh, and here I thought
you were starting to like me again.
你终于舍得走出悲伤
接我电话了
You've deigned to break your despair
long enough to pick up the phone.
我不接你会一直打
I figured you'd just keep calling.
我现在在女巫区
你可以来这里见我
KLAUS: I'm in the cauldron now.
You could meet me here.
我们可以先绑些路人在火刑往上烧
We could start burning
passersby at the stake.
抱歉，我要追踪我自己的线索
Sorry. I'm gonna chase
down my own lead.
那线索在哪里呢？
威士忌的瓶底吗？
And where might that be,
the bottom of a bottle of Scotch?
我在苏菲德弗罗这里
I'm at Sophie Deveraux's place.
我打算就坐在这里一直喝到她出现
I figured I'll sit here
and drink until she shows.
或者你可以从恐惧中摆脱出来
然后来帮我结束这一切
Or you could snap out of this funk
and come and help me end this.
大坏蛋克劳斯米卡森
Big, bad Klaus Mikaelson.
苏菲
Sophie.
恰好是我想要折磨的女巫
Just the witch
I was looking to brutalize.
或许你可以解释一下对我手下的攻击
Perhaps you could explain
the attacks on my men.
蕾贝卡不接电话
Rebekah is not answering her calls.
你担心杀死这些日行者的人
You worried about
whoever killed those Daywalkers
还在外面吗？
still being out there?
坦白说，我是担心她跟这事有关
Frankly, I'm worried that she had
something to do with this.
她对尼克劳斯非常不满
She's very displeased with Niklaus.
或许甚至会和其他人
Perhaps even conspiring...
一起密谋些什么
...with others.
提艾里，是吗？
Thierry, is it?
没错
That's right.
你知道我妹妹非常喜欢你
Do you know,
my sister is rather fond of you.
奇怪，她通常不会被不起眼的男人吸引
Strange, she's not typically
drawn to unremarkable men.
你能解释一下你突如其来的魅力吗？
Would you care to explain
your sudden magnetism?
我不知道你在…
I don't know what you're--
要嘛告诉我你知道些什么
You can either tell me what you know
要嘛我就把你撕碎撒在这片法语区里
or I can distribute tiny pieces
of you throughout the Quarter.
她要我留意女巫的事
She asked me to keep
an eye out on witch stuff.
我所有发现
I found something,
在我带她看时
我们被一个人偷袭了
and when I showed her,
we were jumped by some guy.
他碰到她就把她变干了
He desiccated her with his touch.
你就像个懦夫丢下了她
Like a coward, you left her.
那我该怎么做
和那个能把真祖榨干的巫师
What was I supposed to do,
fight some warlock
打一架吗？
that took out an Original?
这在哪里发生的？
Where was this, exactly?
码头，57号仓库
The docks, warehouse 57.
我只是按她要求去做
你不能把这些告诉克劳斯
I was just doing what she asked.
You cannot tell Klaus about this.
我会考虑的
I shall take that
into consideration.
- 我和你一起去
- 不，留在这里，这里很安全
-I'm coming with you.
-No. Stay here. Compound is safe.
蕾贝卡遇上麻烦了，我要去
Rebekah is in trouble.
I'm going.
不许离开我的视线，明白吗？
Do not leave my sight.
Understand?
你知道，终止和你的关系
并不是因为我不喜欢你
You know. Calling things off with you
wasn't lack of interest.
我只是希望能让你远离这一切
I was hoping
to save you from all this.
谢了，罗密欧，但我已经深陷其中
Well, thanks, Romeo, but I'm in it.
你打算什么时候才会说到
So, when are you gonna get
to the good part
克劳斯还有那个什么巫父的事呢？
with Klaus and that Papa guy?
图德巫父说他想要赋予女巫权利
Papa Tunde said he wanted
to empower the witches.
主要的是，他想要金钱和领土
Mostly, he wanted money
and territory.
克劳斯和以利亚一样都不打算满足他
Klaus and Elijah weren't about
to give him either.
他不喜欢那样，所以他发在了
He didn't like that,
so he went on a rampage.
没人是安全的
No one was safe.
决策群的人类不安全
Not the humans in the faction.
葛雷拉的狼人不安全
MARCEL; Not the Guerrera werewolves.
他甚至去追杀那些反对他的女巫
He even went after the witches
who opposed him.
以利亚提出了休战
事实上，他做出了承诺
Elijah offered a truce.
He gave his word, in fact.
但克劳斯，一如既往，另有打算
But Klaus, being Klaus,
he had another idea.
你迟到了，以利亚
You' re late, Elijah.
高尚的哥哥不会让我久等的
It's not like the noble brother
to keep me waiting.
抱歉，老兄
I'm sorry, mate.
以利亚是在谈判还可能存在时
你所见到的兄弟
Elijah is the brother you meet
when negotiations are to be had.
我则是谈判无效时你会见到的人
I'm the one you get
when negotiations are closed.
你吓不了我
You do not scare me.
你不知道我有多大的力量
You have no idea the power I possess.
事实上，我特别研究了一下
你所有的力量
In fact, I made it a point
to learn all about your power.
我注意到你几乎寸步不离
你的双胞胎儿子
I noticed how you're almost always
near those twin sons of yours.
以及他们为何有你的特殊印记
How they bear your distinctive mark.
这让我不禁思考
Got me to thinking.
你引用了他们的力量，对吧？
You channel their power, don't you?
当然，这就引出了一个问题
Which, of course, begs the question,
如果那些力量被拿走了会怎么样
what would happen
were that power to be taken away,
如果你的儿子们
也就是你力量的来源
if those sons,
whose lives you depend on...
突然被杀死了会怎么样？
...were suddenly struck down...
到时那些力量会怎么样呢？
What of that power then?
- 我要杀了你报仇
- 我是杀不死的
-I will kill you for this.
-I cannot be killed.
然而你…
You, however...
- 太可怕了
- 对克劳斯来说，这只是公事
-That's horrible.
-Oh, to Klaus, it's just business.
难道你不觉得这事
And don't you think
there's something
从根本上就有问题吗？
fundamentally wrong with that?
你就不担心你最后
也会成为他的受害者
Don't you worry you'll end up
one of his victims
或是更糟，变得和他一样？
or, worse, just like him?
可怜的马赛勒斯
TUNDE: Poor Marcellus.
你始终活在你父亲的阴影下
You remain always
in the shadow of your father.
从那下面爬出来吧，行吗？
这样你就能像个男人一样死去
Climb out from beneath it, will you?
So you can die like a man.
卡蜜，你快走
别回头，赶紧走
Cami, you need to run now.
Don't look back. Just go.
我觉得她应该留下
我更喜欢有个观众
I think she should stay.
I prefer an audience
我即将上演一出精彩好戏呢
and I'm about to put on
quite the show.
- 马赛尔？
- 我说了，快离开这里
-CAMl: Marcel?
-I said, get out of here.
你打败不了我的
You cannot defeat me.
我从一个吸血鬼真祖身上获得了力量
I channel the power
of an Original vampire.
很快，我就会获得三个真祖的力量
但首先，我要解决你
Soon, I will have all three,
but first, I will take you.
这是个复杂的咒语
SOPHlE: It's a complex spell.
传统的东西都起源于献祭魔法
Old-school stuff
rooted in sacrificial magic.
不管是谁对你的人干了这事
Whoever did this to your guys,
我猜他们
从祭品中获得了更多力量
my guess is, they were
an offering to gain more power.
杀的人越多，他们就越强大
More guys they kill,
more power they get.
没想到你这么快就打来了
I didn't expect a call
from you so soon.
你得赶紧来卢梭酒吧
You need to get to Rousseau's now.
某个疯子巫医要杀马赛尔
Some lunatic witch doctor
is killing Marcel.
尽可能远离那里
Get as far away from there
as you can.
蕾贝卡
ELlJAH: Rebekah.
怎么回事？
What's happening?
某种边界咒语
Some kind of boundary spell.
有人在利用她的力量
Someone is channeling her.
本来这个过程会致命
Typically, it's a lethal process,
但因为她是真祖，所以她死不了
but because she's an Original,
she cannot die.
相反，她就变成了无尽的力量泉源
Instead, she's an
endless source of power.
那我们该怎么办？
So, what are we supposed to do?
我们必须把她救出来
We have to get her out of there.
我记得，你是少数
As I recall,
you're one of the few people
尼克劳斯米卡森在乎的人之一
Niklaus Mikaelson
ever gave a damn about.
你知道他对我的家人做了什么
You know what he did to my family.
父罪子偿
The sins of the father
are paid for by the son.
我会很乐意告诉克劳斯你是怎么死的
I will take pleasure
in telling Klaus how you died.
我记得杀死了你，我可是很喜欢呢
I remember killing you.
I rather relished it.
再次体验愉悦的回忆多么令人高兴啊
What a joy it is
to relive fond memories.
你来了，很好
TUNDE: You're here. Good.
我可以在你儿子面前收拾你
I can crush you before the eyes
of your son
然后我会把你们两个消灭掉
and then I will consume you both.
这一次，我更强大了
This time, I am stronger.
你没有在听，我们没法进入圈内
You're not listening.
We cannot enter the circle.
有某种限制咒语之类的
There's some kind
of confinement spell or...
如果我不能移动她
我们就无法打破连结
If I can't remove her,
we can't break the link.
这是个迥旋咒
就像是女巫的食谱
It's a convoluted spell.
It's like a witch's recipe.
你可以加入更强烈的材料破坏平街
You can spoil the balance
by adding a more potent ingredient,
一种神秘的黏合剂，我也说不清
a mystical binding agent,
I don't know.
火山灰、岩盐
Volcanic ash, rock salt,
任何够多的东西，还包括嵘蝉的眼睛
anything up to
and including eye of newt.
- 女巫的血呢？
- 你有女巫的血吗？
-What about the blood of a witch?
-Do you have the blood of a witch?
- 我需要你帮个忙
- 孩子
-I need a favor.
-The baby.
她有四分之一女巫血统
She's a quarter witch.
- 他死了吗？
- 快离开这里
-ls he dead?
-Get out of here.
马赛尔死了吗？那家伙杀了他吗？
Is Marcel dead?
Did that guy kill him?
他还没能杀死他
马赛尔需要血液来治愈
He didn't finish him off.
Marcel needs blood to heal.
去，给我从街上拉个人来
Go. Find me someone off the street.
- 我来吧
- 不行
-I'll do it.
-No.
你不行
我不想你被牵扯进这一切里
Not you.
I don't want you involved in this.
你再也不能控制我了，记得吗？
You don't control me anymore,
remember?
没事的，马赛尔
It's okay, Marcel.
没事的，没事的，马赛尔
It's okay.
It's okay, Marcel.
我真该把你怯懦的心脏挖出来
I should rip out your coward heart.
怎么，蕾贝卡？
Why, Rebekah?
我们说好要除掉你哥哥
We made a deal
to take out your brother
但人终归要为自己着想
but at the end of the day,
it's every man for himself.
我受够了这种自私的自恋狂
I am so sick
of self-serving narcissists.
难道一个人就不能忠于盟友吗？
Are men simply incapable
of committing to an alliance?
我告诉过你别搞小动作对付家人
I asked you to cease
these petty moves
但你还是跟这个傻瓜一起密谋策画
against our family,
and yet you conspire with this fool.
这就是你的目的吗？
Is this what it's come to you?
对付你的亲哥哥？
Making moves
against your own blood?
别想羞辱我
Don't you try and shame me.
尼克日渐强大
Nik grows more powerful by the day
你什么都不做却还鼓励他
and you do nothing
but encourage him.
我给他提出了建议，因为对我来说
I offer him my counsel
because it's clear to me
显然他想把这个城市变成我们的家园
that he means
to make the city our home.
也许，领导着这些废物
能够控制住这些冲动
Now, perhaps leading these derelicts
will curb some of these impulses,
能给予他某种程度的幸福
grant him some degree of happiness.
你总是说着尼克的幸福
You always talk of Nik's happiness.
这一千年来，他剥夺了我所有
得到幸福的机会
But for 1,000 years, he has robbed me
of any chance at my own.
那我呢，以利亚？
你就不关心我吗？
What about me, Elijah?
Am I not a concern for you?
以这个家族的名义
我们都有所牺牲，蕾贝卡
We all make sacrifices
in the name of this family, Rebekah,
但你要知道
我绝对不会与你或尼克劳斯作对
but know this. I will never stand
against you or Niklaus.
那海莉呢？
What about Hayley?
我密谋任何事
Nothing I conspire to do,
我的任何背叛，都比不上你对她的感情
none of my treachery
will harm this family
给我们家族造成的伤害
as much as your feelings for her.
你就是个伪君子，以利亚
You're a hypocrite, Elijah.
在爱情和家人之间你选了前者
You would choose love over family
却谴责我做了同样的选择
and then condemn me
for doing the same.
很高兴在这里见到你
Fancy meeting you here.
那个符号已经遍布女巫区了
That symbol is already up
and down the cauldron,
到处都出现了这些符号
more of them popping up everywhere.
我猜图德巫父在圈划领土了
I suppose Papa Tunde
is marking his territory.
- 我听说你也看到他了
- 是的
-I'm told you saw him as well.
-Yeah.
- 勾起了许多回忆
- 最好被埋葬的回忆
-Brought up a lot of memories.
-Memories that are best left buried.
你喝醉了
REBEKAH: You're sauced.
庆祝克劳斯打败了疯狂的图德巫父？
Celebrating Klaus' defeat
of the mad Papa Tunde?
不是庆祝，是在借酒浇愁
Not celebrating, drowning sorrows.
是我把图德带来这里的
I'm the one
who brought Tunde to town.
什么？
What?
我在海外时四处打听了一下
I made some inquiries
while I was abroad,
想找一个极其危险的巫师
I wanted the most dangerous witch
anyone could find.
- 你为什么要那么做？
- 为了你
-Why on earth would you do that?
-For you.
我想如果有像图德这样的狠角色来
I figured if someone as bad
as Tunde comes in,
也许克劳斯就会被赶走
maybe Klaus gets chased off.
至少他就会无暇抽身
Very least, he's occupied enough
来阻止我再次得到你
that he can't stop me
from trying to get you back.
你是想告诉我你要摧毁
You mean to tell me
that you would tear down
我的家族建立的一切
你帮助我们建立的一切
everything my family built,
everything you helped us build,
拿自己的性命冒险
risk your own life...
就为了那一丝我会对你表现
...on the off chance
that I would show you
一点点喜爱之情的可能？
the slightest bit of affection?
我愿意
我也这么做了
I would. I did.
我愿意再做一次
I'd do it again.
克劳斯杀死过上千个像图德这样的人
Klaus has killed a thousand Tundes.
他这一生只真正害怕过一个人
All his life, there's only ever been
one man he has truly feared,
我的父亲麦可
my father, Mikael.
那个追杀吸血鬼的吸血鬼
The vampire who hunts vampires.
如果他来到这里
克劳斯一定会逃走，并永远不再回来
If he came here, Klaus would flee
and never turn back.
我们只需要一个能帮我们找到他的女巫
All we need is a witch
who can help us find him.
不久前，你们联合起来对付我
Not long ago,
you all united against me.
你们失败了
You failed.
从那时起，因为我的仁慈
过去的恩怨就一笔勾销了
Since then, in my benevolence,
I have wiped the slate clean.
然而似乎你们觉得，我才是那个
Yet, it seems clear
you think that I am the one
需要赢得你们的尊重和忠诚的人
who needs to earn your respect,
your loyalty.
你们错了
You're mistaken.
是你们必须向我证明自己
It is you who must
prove yourselves to me.
我们的社区正遭受攻击
Our community is under attack.
我需要士兵
I require soldiers.
我需要勇士而非懦夫
I need warriors, not cowards.
你们好好做决定吧
Each of you has a decision to make.
要么和我并肩作战
You either fight alongside me
要么现在就离开
or you leave now.
我们什么都不欠你
We don't owe you anything!
如果留在法语区意味着
要生活在你的掌控之下
If staying in the Quarter means
living under your rule,
我会尽快离开这里的
I'd just as soon get the hell out.
我得承认
MARCEL: I got to admit,
我以为你会损失更多人呢
I thought you'd lose
a lot more guys than that.
我说，幸好摆脱他们了
Well, good riddance to them, I say.
我们的王国容不下懒汉懦夫
We've no room for slackers
or cowards in our kingdom.
既然你恢复了冷静
Now that you've regained
your composure,
我们就继续下个事项，好吗？
Iet's move on to the next item
of business, shall we?
有我们亲爱的朋友苏菲的小小帮忙
With a little help
from our dear friend, Sophie.
我没理由帮你
I got no reason to help you
我也绝对没理由帮他
and I sure as hell
don't have a reason to help him.
别这么难搞嘛，亲爱的
KLAUS: Now, now, don't be difficult, love.
你对我有用处才能继续活着
You'll only live as long
as you're of use to me,
而现在，你最大的用处就是解释
and right now,
your best use is to explain
为什么一个一百年前被我杀死的巫师
又回来复仇了
why a witch I killed 100 years ago
has come back for revenge.
拜托
拥有强大力量的复活巫师？
SOPHlE: Come on.
Resurrected witches with vast power?
是收获祭
It's the Harvest.
四个女孩照理应该死而复活
Four girls were meant to die
and be reborn.
我不知道怎么做的
但有人劫走了那力量
I don't know how
but someone jacked that power
然复利用它复活了四个巫师
and they used it
to bring back four witches.
只不过不是那四个女孩
Just not the right ones.
所以还有机会
So there's still a chance.
如果我们能够夺回力量，就能救黛维娜
If we can get that power back,
we can save Davina.
我们先把注意力集中在现有的问题上
Let's concentrate
on the immediate problem, shall we?
图德巫父想要复仇
Papa Tunde wants revenge.
他还会攻击我们
He'll continue to attack us,
利用他献祭的吸血鬼的力量
channeling power
from the vampires he sacrifices.
他杀的越多，就会变得越危险
He kills, he grows more dangerous.
我要怎么阻止他？
So, how do I end him?
他需要献祭来获得力量
He needs sacrifices to gain power.
不让他杀死更多的夜行者
You keep him from killing
any more nightwalkers,
就是个好的开始
that's a start.
除非
Unless...
他已经找到了一个地方
那里满是吸血鬼
...he finds the one place
with a load of vampires
随时可以被献祭
ready to be sacrificed.
完成了吗？
Is it done?
这把刀现在包含着
This blade now contains
我从吸血鬼身上收获的力量
all the power I harvested
from the vampires.
它能做到的，是比死亡更可怕的事情
即使是对吸血鬼真祖
It will do things worse than death,
even to an Original.
你准备好最后的献祭了吗？
And are you ready
for the final offering?
以法语区女巫之名
In the name of the witches
of the French Quarter,
这是我的荣幸
it is my honor.
谢谢你，图德巫父
Thank you, Papa Tunde.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）